Guide to the Duke University Progress Pictures Collection, 1925-1932 UA.01.15.0012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- West Campus, 1927-1932
  - West Campus Progress Picture #312, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC312)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #313, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC313)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #314, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC314)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Classroom and Auditorium, with Union Building at right."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #315, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC315)
    From back of photograph: "View showing extension to Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #316, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC316)
    From back of photograph: "View showing extension to Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] at left of picture and extension to 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] at right."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #317, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC317)
    From back of photograph: "View showing Quadrangle front of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] with Group 'B' [Crowell Quadrangle] at right."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #318, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC318)
    From back of photograph: "View showing Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] at left and 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] at right."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #319A, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC319a)
    From back of photographs: "View showing Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] extension."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #319B, 1930 February 5 (Box 4, Print WC319b)
    From back of photograph: "View showing Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] extension."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #320, 1930 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC320)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from the roof of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] showing Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle]." [NB: The photo caption is incorrect. The Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] are pictured.]
  - West Campus Progress Picture #321, 1930 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC321)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from top of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] showing Union Building and School of Religion. Classroom and Auditorium at rear of Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #322, 1930 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC322)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from top of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] showing Union Building, Library and Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #323, 1930 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC323)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School, looking along axis of campus, showing Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building] in foreground."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #324, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC324)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from in front of the Law Building [now Languages Building], showing Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building] and Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #325, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC325)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from in front of the Library Building showing foundation for Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building] ."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #326, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC326)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Chemistry Building location, showing excavation for Chemistry Building and Law Building [now Languages Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #327, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC327)
    From back of photograph: "View showing excavation for Chemistry Building, with Medical School in background."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #328, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC328)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #329, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC329)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] and Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #330, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC330)
    From back of photograph: "View showing extension to Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #331, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC331)
    From back of photograph: "View showing extension to Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] on left and Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] on the right of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #332, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC332)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of [Card] Gymnasium."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #333, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC333)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Auditorium Building, with scaffold around stage."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #334, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC334)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near the Chapel location, showing excavation for Chapel Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #335, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC335)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near the rear of the Chapel, showing foundation excavation for Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #336A, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC336a)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #336B, 1930 March 4 (Box 4, Print WC336b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #337, 1930 April 1 (Box 4, Print WC337)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from top of the Medical School tower looking along Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #338, 1930 April 1 (Box 4, Print WC338)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from top of Medical School tower showing Library Building in center of picture and foundation for Chemistry Building at bottom of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #339, 1930 April 1 (Box 4, Print WC339)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from top of Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] showing Library in center of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #340, 1930 April 1 (Box 4, Print WC340)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from top of Union Building showing Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle], with Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] at right of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #341, 1930 April 1 (Box 4, Print WC341)
    From back of photograph: "View looking North, showing Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] extension and Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle] extension."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #342, 1930 April 1 (Box 4, Print WC342)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from top of School of Religion showing foundation for Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #343, 1930 April 1 (Box 4, Print WC343)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near the rear of Chapel, showing foundation for same. School of Religion on left and Auditorium on right of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #344, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC344)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Library showing front of Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building] and Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #345, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC345)
    From back of photograph: "View showing foundation for Chapel. Forms being built for pouring first floor concrete."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #346, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC346)
    From back of photograph: "View showing location of Chapel, taken from main campus."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #347A, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC347a)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle], showing Union, Library, Law Building [now Languages Building] and Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #347B, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC347b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #348A, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC348a)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from rear of Chapel showing foundation for same."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #348B, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC348b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #349A, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC349a)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Union Building showing Group 'A' [Craven Quadrangle] and 'B' [Crowell Quadrangle] Dormitories."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #349B, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC349b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #350A, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC350a)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from south end of Dormitories showing Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] and Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle] extensions."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #350B, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC350b)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from south end of Dormitories showing Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] and Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle] extensions." [NB: The photo caption is incorrect. The foundation for the Physics Building is on the left.]
  - West Campus Progress Picture #351A, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC351a)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School tower, looking along main Quadrangle. On right is foundation for Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building]." [NB: The photo caption is incorrect. The foundation for the Physics Building is on the left.]
  - West Campus Progress Picture #351B, 1930 May 3 (Box 4, Print WC351b)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School tower, looking along main Quadrangle. On right is foundation for Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #352, 1930 May 23 (Box 4, Print WC352)
    From back of photograph: "View of main campus, taken from Medical School tower."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #353, 1930 May 23 (Box 4, Print WC353)
    From back of photograph: "View showing foundation for Chemistry Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #354A, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC354a)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from top of Medical School tower."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #354B, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC354b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #355, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC355)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from center of Quadrangle showing Chapel foundation."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #356, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC356)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] extension."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #357, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC357)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #358, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC358)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #359, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC359)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Quadrangle showing court in front of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #360, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC360)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Union Building showing Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #361, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC361)
    From back of photograph: "View showing foundation for Chapel, taken from near rear of building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #362, 1930 June 4 (Box 4, Print WC362)
    From back of photograph: "View showing foundation for Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #363A, 1930 July 1 (Box 4, Print WC363a)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School tower, looking along Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #363B, 1930 July 1 (Box 4, Print WC363b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #364, 1930 July 1 (Box 4, Print WC364)
    From back of photograph: 'View taken from Library tower, showing foundation for Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #365, 1930 July 1 (Box 4, Print WC365)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle] tower, showing Library, Law Building [now Languages Building], Chemistry Building and Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #366, 1930 July 1 (Box 4, Print WC366)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Hospital."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #367, 1930 July 1 (Box 4, Print WC367)
    From back of photograph: "View showing Quadrangle in front of Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #368, 1930 July 1 (Box 4, Print WC368)
    From back of photograph: "View showing Quadrangle in front of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #369, 1930 July 2 (Box 4, Print WC369)
    From back of photograph: "View showing spray pond for cooling water for ice plant in Hospital."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #370, 1930 July 2 (Box 4, Print WC370)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near rear of Chapel showing Chapel foundation, Auditorium and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #371, 1930 July 2 (Box 4, Print WC371)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Physics Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #372, 1930 July 2 (Box 4, Print WC372)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #373, 1930 July 2 (Box 4, Print WC373)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] extension."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #374A, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC374a)
    From back of photograph: "View showing the rear of Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle] and Group 'A' Dormitories [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #374B, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC374b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #375, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC375)
    From back of photograph: "View showing location of tennis courts."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #376, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC376)
    From back of photograph: "View showing arcade between Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] and Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #377, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC377)
    From back of photograph: "View showing the tower at Group 'B' Dormitories [Crowell Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #378, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC378)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Quadrangle near Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] looking toward Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #379, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC379)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building] showing Chemistry Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #380, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC380)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from near Library showing Physics Building [now Social Sciences Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #381, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC381)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Law Building [now Languages Building] showing Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #382, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC382)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle], showing North end of main Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #383, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC383)
    From back of photograph: "View showing court in Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #384, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC384)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from School of Religion showing foundation and first floor of Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #385, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC385)
    From back of photograph: "View showing Quadrangle in front of the Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #386A, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC386a)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School tower, showing main Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #386B, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Print WC386b)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #399, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC399)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from Medical School tower, showing top of Chemistry Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #400, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC400)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Chemistry Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #401, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC401)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #402, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC402)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #403, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC403)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Auditorium stage and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #404, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC404)
    From back of photograph: "View showing service road to the rear of Group 'A' [Craven Quadrangle] and 'B' [Crowell Quadrangle] Dormitories."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #405, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC405)
    From back of photograph: "View showing rear of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] next to Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #406, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC406)
    From back of photograph: "View showing new tennis courts under construction."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #407, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC407)
    From back of photograph: "View showing court at the rear of the Union Building, and side of Auditorium."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #408, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC408)
    From back of photograph: "View showing front of Medical School and front of Botany and Zoology Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #409, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC409)
    From back of photograph: "View taken from tower of Chapel, looking to the rear."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #410, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC410)
    From back of photograph: "Picture taken from near School of Religion, showing front of Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #411, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC411)
    From back of photo: "View showing rear of Chemistry Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #412, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC412)
    From back of photo: "View taken from top of terrace, looking toward Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] tower."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #413, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC413)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] Tower looking North along Main Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #414, 1930 September 1 (Box 4, Print WC414)
    From back of photo: "View taken from front of Medical School. looking South along Main Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #415, 1931 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC415)
    From back of photo: "View taken from rear of Chapel, looking toward front of same."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #416, 1931 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC416)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near center of Chapel showing top of arch windows in Memorial Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #417, 1931 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC417)
    From back of photo: "View showing columns in the crypt under the Memorial Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #418, 1931 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC418)
    From back of photo: "View taken from tower of Union Building, showing Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #419, 1931 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC419)
    From back of photo: "View taken from tower of Library, showing front of Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #420, 1931 February 6 (Box 4, Print WC420)
    From back of photo: "View taken from rear of the Botany Building [now Sociology-Psychology Building], showing location of greenhouses." [NB: This photo is dated 1931-02-09 on the front and 1931-02-06 on the back.]
  - West Campus Progress Picture #421, 1931 April 17 (Box 4, Print WC421)
    From back of photo: "View showing interior of Chapel. Large window in the rear of Choir."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #422, 1931 April 17 (Box 4, Print WC422)
    From back of photo: "View showing details of interior of Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #423, 1931 April 17 (Box 4, Print WC423)
    From back of photo: "View showing details of limestone - interior of Chapel."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #424, 1931 April 17 (Box 4, Print WC424)
    From back of photo: "View showing front of the Chapel, taken from Administration Building [now Flowers Building]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #425, 1931 April 17 (Box 4, Print WC425)
    From back of photo: "View showing exterior of Chapel, taken from Library Tower."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #426, 1931 May 13 (Box 4, Print WC426)
    From back of photo: "View showing greenhouses being erected at Duke University."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #427, 1931 October 10 (Box 4, Print WC427)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Nurses Home [Baker House] looking toward Hospital, showing steam and water mains for supplying Nurses Home."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #428, 1931 October 10 (Box 4, Print WC428)
    From back of photo: "View taken from the North looking South, showing first floor of Nurses Home [Baker House]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #429, 1931 October 10 (Box 4, Print WC429)
    From back of photo: "View taken from the East looking West, showing first floor of Nurses Home [Baker House]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #430, 1932 February 26 (Box 4, Print WC430)
    From back of photo: "View showing front of Nurses Home [Baker House]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #431, 1932 February 26 (Box 4, Print WC431)
    From back of photo: "View showing front of Nurses Home [Baker House], taken from end nearest Hospital."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #432, 1932 February 26 (Box 4, Print WC432)
    From back of photo: "View showing side of Nurses Home [Baker House] next to Hospital."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #433, 1932 February 26 (Box 4, Print WC433)
    From back of photo: "View showing Main Entrance to University with Chapel in the center of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #434, 1932 March 17 (Box 4, Print WC434)
    From back of photo: "View showing Base Ball Field, Duke University."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #435, 1932 April 6 (Box 4, Print WC435)
    From back of photo: "Picture showing front of console for the Aeolian Organ, Duke Chapel. Picture taken before console set in place."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #436, 1932 April 8 (Box 4, Print WC436)
    Quarry
  - West Campus Progress Picture #437, 1932 April 8 (Box 4, Print WC437)